SAWARNEE SETHI

1227, RANI BAGH, DELHI - 110034 · (91) 7042725575 · SAWARNEE1997@GMAIL.COM

I am a Computer Science Engineering student, constantly learning different technologies and upgrading myself. I am good in software and web development and have made many projects using different technologies. Apart from the development, I am also good in communication (spoken and written) and possess good leadership qualities . I am good in representing something effectively and love to take part in challenges and hackathons. I want to be an entrepreneur and I think that work exposure and experience gained during this time will help me a lot to achieve my dream.





EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

AIRPORTS AUTHORITY OF INDIA

I developed a seperate web portal for monitoring of different projects (initiated, under development, and completed) at different Indian Airports.

June 2018 - July 2018

WEB DESIGN INTERN

ARBUNIZE

I reviewed and edit front end codes of the main website of the company - getboarded.com

December 2017 - March 2018

EDUCATION

BHAGWAN PARSHURAM INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (IPU)

B.TECH

Computer Science Engineering Percentage: 80.42%

August 2015 - May 2019

D.L.D.A.V MODEL SCHOOL, PITAMPURA

HIGHER SECONDAY EDUCATION (12TH)

Central Board of Secondary Education Percentage: 92.25%

2014 - 2015

D.L.D.A.V MODEL SCHOOL, PITAMPURA

MATRICULATION (10TH)

Central Board of Secondary Education CGPA: 9.6

2012 - 2013

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TOOLS



















- ✓ Full Stack Web Development
- ✓ Java & J2EE
- ✓ DBMS (SQL Databases)
- ✓ Software Development
- ✓ AWS Web hosting (Elastic Beanstalk & RDS services)

PROJECTS

FINANCIAL SERVICES RECOMMENDATION ENGINE

A web portal which suggests offline shops and online portals to users according to their age, gender, locality, monthly income, monthly exenditure etc. The machine learning algorithm takes different inputs from the user and then on its basis, suggest recommendations.

View on Github

WEB PORTAL FOR MONITORING OF DIFFERENT PROJECTS AT INDIAN AIRPORTS

AIRPORTS AUTHORITY OF INDIA

A web portal for monitoring of different projects at Indian airports. Users can view the initiatives, under development and completed projects on the website. Simultaneusly, operators and admin can open their account and can do their respective tasks. Admin can add or delete or modify operator's or airport's information while operator can add or delete or modify the projects of that particular airport.

View on Github

ONLINE REGISTRATION SYSTEM

A complete web application through which students can store their confidentials such as marksheets and other information online and in response, they will receive a qr code. They have to show this qr code to the operator at the time of admission and on scanning this code, operator will obtain all the files and information on his system and he can manage them in any order he needs. This project also inlude Forget Password and QR code generator modules.

Click to view video of running project

View on Github

INTERESTS

hanging out with friends.

When forced indoors, I follow a number of sci-fi and fantasy genre movies and television shows, I like to play guitar and video games, and I spend a large amount of my free time exploring the latest technology advancements in different fields.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Y Won gold medal in badminton(singles and doubles) for 2 consecutive years at College Annual sports meet.

Coordinated a complete sports event(badminton) at the College Annual sports meet.